pullapart.com 2019-01-25

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At Pull-A-Part, LLC, Inc. your data and its security and our use of it is important. We realize that you may have concerns regarding the privacy of your personal information. This is why we have specifically created this section; to address any concerns and questions you may have.

This Customer Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for Pull-A-Part, LLC retail stores (the "Stores"), Pull-A-Part, LLC Customer Care centers (the "Call Centers"), www.pullapart.com and www.partart.com websites (the "Sites"), our platform all other locations, occasions, or events where your personal information is collected by, or on behalf of Pull-A-Part, LLC.

Pull-A-Part, LLC regularly reviews and updates its privacy policy and practices.

The uses of information collected through our services shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the client has engaged Pull-A-Part LLC and its affiliates.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or our practices, please contact us at [(678) 993-2500](https://www.google.com/search?q=Pull-A-Part+Corporate+Office&stick=H4sIAAAAAAAAAONgecSYyS3w8sc9YamESWtOXmOM4uIKzsgvd80rySypFPLhYoOyFLj4pbj10_UNS1IMTCssjTUYpHi5kAWkFJS4eJm2WYiI5vUePqslxMkABYIlJdJ8k-6nuPEAAFlsrwduAAAA&sa=X&ved=0ahUKEwiM4Yj93LLZAhUD7VMKHcDjDm4Q6RMIiwEwCw&biw=1628&bih=861 "Call via Hangouts") or online.

**Personal Information We Collect**

As part of your interaction with Pull-A-Part, LLC, we may collect personal information such as name, email address, billing address, mailing address and phone number.

**When We Collect Personal Information**

  * We may collect personal information from you when you:
  * Create an account on our Site
  * Purchase, return, or exchange items in our Stores, interact with us through our Call Centers, or on our websites
  * Contact one of our Call Centers
  * Utilize one of our in-store services
  * Subscribe to our newsletter or emails
  * Respond to a survey or fill out a form
  * Register for a product warranty
  * Sign up for a loyalty program
  * Enter into a contest or sweepstakes
  * Provide us with reviews, questions, answers, comments, feedback, or suggestions

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

The personal information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways:

**To enhance your experience**

Your information helps us to enhance and personalize your shopping experience in our Stores, through our Call Centers, and on our Sites. We may use your personal information to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers, to improve the content of our Sites for you, and to improve your Store and Call Center experience.

**To improve customer service**

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. Based upon the information you provide us when creating an account on our Sites, we may send you a welcoming email to verify your information. We will also communicate with you to respond to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.

**To process transactions**

We use your information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we may use your information to contact you.

**To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other feature, such as on a Site**

From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys, including on our Sites. If you participate, we will request certain information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address, phone number, and/or email address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor Site traffic or personalize the Site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), or to send participants an email related to the contest, promotion or survey (such as reminder or thank you notices).

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; such companies are prohibited from using our users' information for any other purpose. We will not share the information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**To send periodic communications**

We may send you mail, email, text, or call you with information about our product and service offerings if you have provided us with your name and address, email address or phone numbers at our Stores, Call Centers, or Sites.

If you place an order or enroll in a program in Store or on our Sites, the contact information you provide will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or in accordance with any other opt-in you may elect. If you decide to opt-in to our loyalty (e.g. VIP program) or our promotional email list, you will receive emails that may include company news, program information, offers, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future promotional emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each promotional email. Please reference the Opt-Out section of the Pull-A-Part, LLC Privacy Policy below. As always, you may also contact us via phone, email, or regular mail.

**To send service-related announcements**

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, please notify us by email phone or regular mail.

**To Email / Refer a Friend**

If you choose to use any referral service we launch to tell a friend about our Sites, Products, Services, or Programs, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. Pull-A-Part, LLC does not store your friend's name or email address in our database, unless your friend elects to opt-into communications from or with Pull-A-Part, LLC.

**Opting out of Communication**

If you would like to opt-out of communication from Pull-A-Part, LLC, we will ask you to select from several different options. Please note: order confirmation communications, Loyalty Program, Notify Me, Receipt, Rating & Review / Survey, and Reminder communications are considered transactional messages. Further, you may choose to maintain promotional messages from different programs or channels.

If you prefer to opt out of any of the marketing messages above, you may email us at here, through any available www.pullapart.com loyalty program or communication preferences pages or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail by clicking the Contact Us link at the bottom of this page.

Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change by visiting one of our stores or by contacting us by postal mail or by clicking the Contact Us link at the bottom of this page.

**Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews**

We may post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as customer first name. If you wish to update or delete any testimonial, you can contact us here. In rare cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Blog**

Our Web site may offer publicly accessible blogs. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, please contact us. In rare cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

In general, we may combine your personal information with non-personal information collected through our Stores, Call Centers, Sites, and/or third party sources in order to accomplish the uses listed above.

**Security - How We Protect Your Information**

At Pull-A-Part, LLC we leverage some of the most cutting edge technology and practices to maintain the security of customer information. Our security measures meet or exceed both industry and regulatory standards and we proactively look for ways to improve our processes.

In order to help protect your information, we utilize a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information and login credentials is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider's database. Information is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems. Authorized individuals are required to keep the information confidential. Protecting your information is of the utmost importance and we do not take our responsibility to our customers lightly.

Regretfully, no form of electronic communication can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Subsequently, although we will utilize our resources to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Under no circumstance does Pull-A-Part, LLC accept or assume liability for any damages whatsoever associated with personal information received.

**How We Share Your Information Outside Pull-A-Part, LLC**

We share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, collections processing, promotional services, etc. We call these our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We may disclose some of your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities who may seek to cause injury to you, Pull-A-Part, LLC, or others. We will disclose your personally identifiable information when required to by law through properly served subpoena only if we believe it necessary.

While rare, from time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities that we believe trustworthy. These are known as our Marketing Partners. In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including some information about you, to enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. We only share the information we believe is appropriate to enable the Marketing Partners to carry out their responsibilities under our contracts, and we require that the information be used only for the specifically authorized purpose and that its confidentiality be maintained.

We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners for research and industry reports. This information does not identify individual users. As a customary practice, we do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

In addition to the information above, we also may collect data on customer shopping patterns while on our Sites. This may include how frequently our Sites are visited, the length of those visits, and the types of items our customers are looking for. This is collected to help improve the current and future shopping experience of you, our customer.

**Your Right Not To Have Your Personal Information Shared**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. You have the choice to be excluded from our offers and promotions and to be excluded from sharing personal information with our Marketing Partners and/or our Service Providers. If you choose not to receive information from us, please reference the Opt-Out section above. Please be sure to include your email address, full name, phone number(s), Loyalty Program (VIP) number, and specifically what information you do not want to receive, such as "no phone offers", "no mail offers", "no email offers", or "no sharing of information with partners". DO NOT include your Social Security number or account number in the email.

We will respond to reasonable requests within 10 days, but please note that sometimes these requests may take up to 6-8 weeks to be effective, particularly if we are removing your name from postal mailings. In addition, when you purchase from us in our Stores, through our Call Centers, or engage on our Sites, we may need to contact you via phone, email, or mail, to address questions specific to your order, even if you have opted to not receive communications.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

This Privacy Policy describes how we share information for marketing purposes. Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, Pull-A-Part, LLC provides its California customers the ability to exercise "opt out" rights as follows:

You may exercise your "opt out" rights, at no charge, by sending us an email at customersupport@pullapart.com.

**Third Party Links**

Within our Site you may find links to websites of our partners, vendors, or advertisers. It is important to note that Pull-A-Part, LLC does not endorse or make any statement to the security of the websites that we provide links to. These websites have independent security policies, privacy policies, technology and security practices of their own. We do not have control over their content or their security and do not accept liability of any form for the manner in which they protect and/or handle your information. We recommend that all consumers comprehensively review the privacy policy of each website that they visit to help keep them informed on how their personal information is treated and used.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site may include Social Media Features, such as Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Cookies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts may be used by Pull-A-Part, LLC and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics / service providers (e.g. to provide online customer support and data to improve the online customer shopping experience). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering sites, tracking users' movements, and receiving reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We may use cookies to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference), for targeted messaging, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting**

We may partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner may use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by contacting us online. Please note this will not opt you out of being served advertising. You may continue to receive generic ads.

**Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track users' movements around the Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We use local storage HTML 5 (LSOs) to store content information and preferences.

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use LSOs to collect and store information.

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

**Email Privacy**

Email is not a secure means of communication under most circumstances. Never provide sensitive personal information (i.e. Social Security number, driver's license number, or third party credit card information) to us via email.

Pull-A-Part, LLC will not sell, trade, share or rent the email address, phone numbers, or mailing addresses you provide to anyone. We believe that your contact information is personal and should be kept that way. We use your numbers and addresses to provide you with better customer support, and to update you on specials.

**Chat Feature**

Should we deploy an optional chat feature, it will be to assist you with using the website. We do not request or collect any personally identifiable information unless it is necessary for assisting you with your specific problem.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your loyalty program account (e.g. VIP) is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us here. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If it is discovered that we have collected personally identifiable information from someone under 13 we will delete that information immediately.

**Terms and Conditions**

Terms and Conditions establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site may be published from time to time. Should you need more detailed information on our Terms & Conditions, please contact us. 

**Your Consent**

By using our Site, you (the user) agree to our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Additionally, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Pull-A-Part, LLC as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

This policy was last modified on February 19, 2018.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:

Pull-A-Part, LLC, Inc.

4473 Tilly Mill Rd.

Doraville, GA 30360

Or by submitting a question online: Contact Us
